Season's Greetings and Merry Christmas to Emmanuel TV Partners
from the Mayor of Bethlehem
Greetings from Bethlehem to Prophet T.B. Joshua
Merry Christmas From Bethlehem!
Church of the Nativity
Bethlehem
The Birthplace of
JESUS CHRIST
To my dear friend T.B. Joshua,
general overseer of The Synagogue Church Of All Nations,
Merry Christmas from the city and the capital of Christmas - from the city of Bethlehem.
This year our message to Bethlehem was delivered on the 3rd of December,
calling for peace, love and hope - the main message of Bethlehem.
Ringing the bells, the lighting of the tree will keep Bethlehem alive.
Being with us is very important,
to keep the message alive as long as Bethlehem is alive and divided.
Merry Christmas and Happy New Year to you all,
to all prophets, supporters...
Thank you very much for supporting Bethlehem as well.
To my dear friend T.B. Joshua,
on behalf of the Franciscans in the Holy Land and the local Christians
I would like to wish you a very Merry Christmas and a Happy New Year both to you and your family,
and to the members of your great church.
We know that you have a great love for the church in the Holy Land
and we look forward to being with you in a week or two to show you the many programmes
that we are doing to help the Christians in the Holy Land.
God bless you, and I'm looking forward to seeing you again.
Merry Christmas
♩ Long time ago in Bethlehem, so the Holy Bible says ♩
♩ Mary's boy child Jesus Christ was born on Christmas Day ♩
RV: Mel Flowers 27/03/2019